(Sheldon:)Well, this sandwich
is an unmitigated disaster.
(Sheldon:)I asked for turkey and roast beef...
- ...with lettuce and Swiss on whole wheat.
- What'd they give you?
(Sheldon:)Turkey and roast beef
with Swiss and lettuce on whole wheat.
(Sheldon:)It's the right ingredients
but in the wrong order.
(Sheldon:)In a proper sandwich,
the cheese is adjacent to the bread...
(Sheldon:)...to create a moisture barrier
against the lettuce.
(Sheldon:)They might as well have dragged this thing
through a car wash.
- I don't believe it.
- I know. It's basic culinary science.
(Leonard:)Some guy is auctioning off
a miniature time-machine prop...
(Leonard:)...from the original film
and no one is bidding.
(Howard:)A time machine
from the movie The Time Machine?
(Leonard:)No, a time machine
from Sophie's Choice.
(Raj:)Boy, Sophie could have used
a time machine in that movie.
Did you see it? It's rough.
HOWARD: Oh, that's cool.
LEONARD: Uh-huh.
- It's only $800?
- Yeah. And that's my bid.
- You bid $800?
- It was a spur-of-the-moment thing.